GENELFF

I am a junior web developer with 3+ years of experience developing user interfaces, debugging code, testing, and managing websites. I am a quick learner, and am looking forward to learning new programs and skills throughout my career.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Entry Level Software

05/2018 - present

Engineer

Dulles Glass & Mirror, Manassas, United States

- Developed and maintained multiple ecommerce websites in both the frontend and backend using ASP .NET MVC Framework
- Updated database and managed inventory
- · Implemented key new features into the websites and fixed bugs
- Updated websites to a new mobile responsive design
- Managed the company's Amazon seller central account

Software and Test Engineer Intern

12/2016 - 05/2018

Dulles Glass & Mirror, Faifax, United States

- Implemented front-end code (web design) for multiple ecommerce websites/applications as a web developer.
- · Worked with the ASP.NET framework, C#, and Amazon Web Services (DynamoDB, S3). Tested software for web applications.
- Experience working and cooperating with a team, managing inventory, and developing in both front and back end.
- Worked closely with senior developer and trained under him

Programmer & Level Designer

08/2017 - 05/2018

Computer Game Design Senior Capstone, Fairfax, **United States**

- · Worked on a unique game experience in a team of 3, for a year-long project.
- Managed and developed the game concept and mechanics from start to finish.
- Developed on the Unity 3Dgame engine with C#, using models made in 3DS Max and Autodesk Maya.

EDUCATION

09/2013 - 05/2018 **B.S. Economics** George Mason University, Fairfax, United States

Minors in Information Technology and Computer **Game Design**

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2013 - MAY 2018

• GPA: 3.27

CERTIFICATIONS

Project Management

2007

Institute for Business Development

SKILI S

Programming languages

Java, Javascript, C#, Python, SQL

Web Technologies

Rest, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, ¡Query, JSON, ASP .NET MVC

Data Management

MySQL, DynamoDB, Microsoft Server Management Studio

KEYWORDS

Adaptable

Attention to detail

Artistic

Communication

Creativity

Learning

Teamwork

Problem-solving

Multitasking

SOCIAL MEDIA



LinkedIn

Portfolio